<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="org.nodeclipse.bundle.coffee_script.feature"
      label="Coffee-script"
      version="1.6.3.qualifier">

   <description url="http://coffeescript.org/">
      CoffeeScript is a little language that compiles into JavaScript. Underneath that awkward Java-esque patina, JavaScript has always had a gorgeous heart. CoffeeScript is an attempt to expose the good parts of JavaScript in a simple way.

The golden rule of CoffeeScript is: &quot;It&apos;s just JavaScript&quot;. The code compiles one-to-one into the equivalent JS, and there is no interpretation at runtime. You can use any existing JavaScript library seamlessly from CoffeeScript (and vice-versa). The compiled output is readable and pretty-printed, will work in every JavaScript runtime, and tends to run as fast or faster than the equivalent handwritten JavaScript.
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://coffeescript.org/">
      Copyright (c) 2009-2013 Jeremy Ashkenas
   </copyright>

   <license url="http://www.example.com/license">
      Copyright (c) 2009-2013 Jeremy Ashkenas

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person
obtaining a copy of this software and associated documentation
files (the &quot;Software&quot;), to deal in the Software without
restriction, including without limitation the rights to use,
copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the
Software is furnished to do so, subject to the following
conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be
included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED &quot;AS IS&quot;, WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND,
EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES
OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND
NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT
HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING
FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR
OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="org.nodeclipse.bundle.coffee-script"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
